mamaway.com 2014-03-21

# Mamaway USA Stylish Maternity clothes | Maternity Jeans | Nursing Tops | Nursing Lingerie | Baby Ring Slings | Thanks Giving

At Mamaway USA Inc. we recognize that privacy is important. This Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Mamaway USA Inc.

If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website or write to us at Privacy Matters, c/o Mamaway USA Inc. 4950 MacArthur Blvd, Suite 500, Newport Beach CA 92660-2028, United States.

You may browse our websites without revealing any personal information about yourself. This is called anonymous access. When you browse our websites as an anonymous user, we collect information about your visit to make the site more useful to all of our visitors and to help grow our business.

The information we collect during the anonymous access visit includes:

Visiting domains

Internet addresses of the domains from which people visit to track a user’s session

Browser type and operating system of the visitor

Date, time and length of the visit

We do not sell, exchange or publish this information; however, we do share this information with specific internal employees and consultants who assist in the implementation and maintenance of our websites.

In some sections of our websites we ask that you voluntarily provide information about yourself. The information you provide may include personally identifiable information such as your name, your address, your telephone number and your e-mail address. By submitting this information, you agree that Mamaway USA Inc. may keep a record of the information in order to respond to requests; send you information on the latest Mamaway USA Inc. products, promotions, and events. Therefore, you agree that Mamaway USA Inc. may disclose the information to Mamaway employees, consultants, and any other third party, in order to respond appropriately to your request or to comply with any legal requirements. We will not sell or otherwise disclose your information to third parties except as expressly permitted by this policy.

We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to otherwise specifically tailor your experience on the site. We use reasonable security measures, such as encryption and firewalls, to ensure against the loss, misuse or alteration of the information under our control.

This site contains links to other sites on the Internet. We are not responsible for the content or privacy practice of any other Internet sites.

Mamaway USA Inc. only processes personal information for the purposes described in the applicable Privacy Policy and/or privacy notice for specific services. In addition to the above, such purposes include:

  * Providing our products and services to users;
  * Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services;
  * Developing new services.

Mamaway USA Inc. processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country. We may process personal information to provide our own services.

If Mamaway USA Inc. becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

Please contact us at the address below for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data.

Privacy Matters: Mamaway USA Inc. 4950 MacArthur Blvd, Suite 500, Newport Beach CA 92660-2028, United States.

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to Mamaway employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

Mamaway USA Inc. processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

Mamaway USA Inc. regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. Please feel free to direct any questions or concerns regarding this Policy or Mamaway USA Inc's treatment of personal information by contacting us through this web site or by writing to us at Privacy Matters, c/o

Mamaway USA Inc. 4950 MacArthur Blvd, Suite 500, Newport Beach CA 92660-2028, United States.

When we receive formal written complaints at this address, it is Mamaway USA Inc's policy to contact the complaining user regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between Mamaway USA Inc. and an individual.

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes). Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date.

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this web site or at Privacy Matters, c/o 

Mamaway USA Inc. 4950 MacArthur Blvd, Suite 500, Newport Beach CA 92660-2028, United States.
